Guide to the New York University Archives Collection on Faculty and Alumni Memory Projects MC.226
New York University Archives
- Series III. Brian Huggins Undergraduate Student Life in Washington Square Project, 1977-1979; 1.50 Linear Feet 1 manuscript box, 1 cassette box, and 2 items in a shared cassette box; 34 audiocassette
  - Kostelanetz, Boris, September 13, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0054)
    - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Kotcher, Harry A. -- Original Recording, December 6, 1977 (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0055)
  - Kreidmann, Arthur -- Correspondence, Notes, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Krugman, Sylvia Stern -- Correspondence, Notes, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Lawrence, Stella, December 29, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0056)
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0057)
    - Correspondence, Notes (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Leffler, Marvin, November 28, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0058)
    - Correspondence, Notes (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Lehon, Hyman, 1977-1978
    - Original Recording, November 11, 1977 (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0059)
    - Original Recording, November 11, 1977 (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0060)
    - Transcript, Correspondence, Notes (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Lind, Ilse, December 12, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0061)
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0062)
    - Transcript (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Lyons, Laurance -- Original Recording, September 20, 1977 (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0063)
  - Millett, Frederick, November 21, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0064)
    - Correspondence, Notes (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Nelson, Lorin -- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - O'Gara, James V., January 13, 1978
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0065)
    - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Rubenfeld, Sidney, November 10, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0066)
    - Correspondence, Notes (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Rubino, A. Vincent, December 16, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0067)
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0068)
    - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Schaps, David -- Original Recording, November 1, 1977 (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0069)
  - Schnaebele, Ernest, October 26, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0070)
    - Correspondence, Notes (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Schuman, Clifford, August 29, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0071)
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Audiocassette 226_0072)
    - Transcript, Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Tauritz, Leo L., November 14, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box Shared University Archives 151, Audiocassette 266_0073)
    - Notes (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Wilson, Edward D., October 26, 1977
    - Original Recording (Box Shared University Archives 151, Audiocassette 266_0074)
    - Correspondence, Notes (Box 5, Folder 32)